rameşaliyev

Computer Scientist

I'm Ramesh, a former Software Engineer from Istanbul who mostly experienced in Web Technologies. I've worked in various companies as Lead and Senior Software Engineer. Currently I'm a Computer Science student at YTU. I'm interested in AI and mostly Computer Vision.

education

BSc, Computer Science Yildiz Technical University (2019 - 2023)

ASc, Computer Programming Sakarya University (2016 - 2018)

High School, Electronics
Zeytinburnu Industrial Vocational High School (2004 - 2007)

publications

Age Estimation from Pediatric Panoramic Dental Images with CNNs and LightGBM 2022. TIPTEKNO'22 Medical Technologies Congress, Antalya, Turkey, pp.105-108. Rames Aliyev, Emre Arslanoglu, Yasin Yasa, Ayse Betul Oktay.

certifications

Fundamentals of Deep Learning NVIDIA, Deep Learning Institute (2021)

Data Science Math Skills Coursera, Duke University (2020)

experiences

Undergraduate Research Fellow - Yildiz Technical University
Jun 2022 - Present

Co-Founder & Full Stack Developer - Ecma Co. Ltd. Jun 2017 - Jun 2021 (4 years)

Senior Full Stack Developer - Omma Sep 2018 - Nov 2020 (2 year 3 months)

Senior Frontend Developer - Pisano

Feb 2018 - Sep 2018 (8 months)

Lead Full Stack Developer - Emlakjet

Jan 2016 - Oct 2017 (1 year 10 months)

Senior JavaScript Developer - Turkcell

Oct 2013 - Dec 2015 (2 years 3 months)

JavaScript Developer - E-NET Internet Technology Co.

Jan 2013 - Sep 2013 (9 months)

Frontend Developer - Techpoint Labs

Mar 2012 - Jan 2013 (11 months)

Full Stack Developer - Koridor Design Studio

Feb 2009 - Mar 2012 (3 years 2 months)

links

rames.dev

github.com/ramesaliyev

linkedin.com/in/ramesaliyev

contact

ramesaliyev@gmail.com